A Team
D Team
Has she been making
all the shots by herself?
Prince powers unleashed, I suppose.
The quadratic equation is written
in vertex form as y = a(x-p)² + q,
Mathematics I
and its vertex is at (p, q).
From this, we can determine that the
vertex of the given function is (-2, 3).
Wow.
C-Correct.
That's our prince, perfect all around.
S-So cool!
Are you all right?
Y-Yes...
Yoi-chan.
Did something happen?
Huh? What're you talking about?
It just feels like you're trying
really hard to distract yourself.
You're running your
prince powers on full blast.
What do you mean, prince powers?
What, you brought gyoza
for lunch and not shumai?
Gyoza...
Hey, I'm going to go buy a drink!
Yep, something sure is goin' on.
Oh, not happening. I can't reach it.
I'm telling you, we need a racket.
Here you go.
Thank you very much!
Hey, isn't she the one called
the first-year Prince?
I've heard of her!
Yep, gotta say, she definitely
looks like a boy at first glance.
These types of occurrences were
the norm in my daily life.
But...
Oh, hey. Isn't that Prince
Ichimura over there?
What? Where, where?
Oh, man. It wasn't him.
Oh, boo.
I can't hide my inner turmoil.
Something inside of me has been
changing ever since I met Senpai.
Oh, I hate this.
I keep thinking, "This isn't like me.
This is stupid."
I blush every time I think about
the things we did together.
I start wishing I could erase
the memories from his head too...
Hey!
You're not gonna go visit
the Prince today?
Uh...
What? Did you do something
that she didn't like again?
Don't think I did, but...
Um... I didn't necessarily...
I wonder what would
have come after that?
Man, this is the first time I've ever
thought about someone this much.
The whole dating thing, right?
It starts somehow. You have some fun.
And, well, then it ends somehow.
Wasn't it always that simple?
You'd think, "Oh, maybe
this one is good."
Or, "This one is probably over."
It's all pretty predictable.
No jealousy involved or strings attached.
There was never a time
when I'd get sappy.
Huh?
I was pretty excited there, wasn't I?
...chi. Ichi!
Hurry up, man.
Lunch is about to end.
Why are you staring off
into space like that?
Oh.
Nah.
It's nothing.
Oh, man.
Ichimura-senpai never came.
What a bummer.
It's not a bummer.
It was nice and quiet.
Sheesh, there you go again, Yoi-chan.
Hey, you know what I just realized?
When you're with Ichimura-senpai,
your prince side never shows.
Oh! And that's why she was exploding
with prince power today! I see!
Yep, yep! When she's with Senpai, her
girly side naturally comes out, y'know?
Aww, the youthful journey!
Youthful
The joys of adolescence!
Adolescence
C-Could you guys cut it out?!
Oh... Sorry.
I didn't mean to say it so loud.
No, we're sorry, too.
Sorry.
I'm just not used to
people calling me girly.
It doesn't sit right, and
it's really embarrassing.
For a moment, somewhere
in my heart, I had my hopes up.
I never would have thought I was the kind
of person who would think like that.
But maybe someone more
prince-like than you
might actually be a better match for you.
Sis was saying that,
but could it be true?
What if I'm just being
influenced by the first person
that happened to appear in front of me?
Would that mean it could have happened
with anyone? Not just Senpai?
Nasu Oyaji Curry
Do I know him?
No, that can't be it.
On the way home, let's stop by
the new store that just opened.
Oh, right on.
Sorry, I have work.
Wha? You do?
Don't tell me you asked for more hours?
Yeah... To clear my mind
of distractions.
Distraction
Does it have something
to do with Ichimura-senpai?
No comment.
Excuse me, would it be all right if
my class used the library as well?
Yes, go right ahead.
No way! It's Ichimura-senpai's class!
Hey! What are you doing,
looking away like that?!
At least go say hi to him!
But we're still in the
middle of class, so...
I suppose this is what we call fate.
Well, thank you kindly.
Been a while since you've gotten
an eyeful of the prince.
Stop making it sound dirty.
Did you wanna talk to her?
Nah, it's not polite to bother her.
Huh?
That's weird.
He usually pulls something by now...
Well, I'm the one telling him
he's not allowed to talk to me.
Frequently Tested Questions (Exam Prep Edition)
Complete Collection of
Ancient Texts
Questions
Besides, we're in the middle of class.
Yeah...
Then, just now...
Maybe I shouldn't have looked away?
I know it's incredibly selfish
and self-centered of me, but...
To be honest...
I felt a little lonely and such...
Mumble
Seriously though,
why am I thinking about all this stuff
just because he ignored me this one time?
I would have never thought this
even for a moment before.
Ichi?
New message from K-san
What? What's wrong?
I'm sorry. I'm getting distracted
because you're here.
It feels like a parent
classroom observation day.
Ichimura!
My b.
Stop making me laugh.
Hey.
Today after school,
would you like to go somewhere?
I'm sorry. I have work today.
Okay, got it.
Okay, class dismissed.
Second-years, we'll stay
here for next period,
so be sure to leave your things.
Let's go, Yoi-chan.
Yeah.
Are you sure you don't want
to say something before we go?
Nobara!
She's right, y'know.
Flutter
Flutter...
Huh?!
Flutter
You better stop messing around, Sentaro!
Forget everything you
just saw, ya bastard!
Sounds like something's going on.
Puberty at its finest, I'd say.
Ichimura, quiet down!
Then. We'll. Go. Next. Time?
Why am I feeling this way
when all we did was make eye contact?
Senpai's sugar-sweet smile.
I kinda...
like it.
I guess he meant it when he
said he wasn't much of a planner.
I wonder where he planned
on going after school.
Exactly when is "next time?"
It's been awhile since we
started this experiment.
Excuse me.
Huh?
That girl. Could she be...?
Could you please let me through?
Are you all right?
Oh... Th-Thank you very much.
Sure. No worries.
Amazing.
He handled that in a very smooth,
sophisticated way, huh?
He's the one from the other day.
Huh?
Nasu Oyaji Curry
Huh?!
Oh, you're here already... Hmm?
Yoi is with you, too?
Oh... Hello?
Ah, sorry about that.
I didn't introduce you guys, huh?
This is Takuto Oji-kun, the new hire.
Nice to meet you.
And this is my daughter, Yoi.
Oh, likewise.
So, with that, if you have any
questions, please ask Yoi, okay?
Understood.
Oh, he's a new hire.
Um...
I'll do my best, and I look
forward to working with you.
S-Same...
Nasu Oyaji Curry
Thank you for waiting.
A vegetable curry and a chicken curry.
Oh... Thank you.
He's charming them.
That Oji-kun is pretty handsome.
This one is the vegetable curry, and...
Planning on starting an idol agency?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I know, right?
Now, I'd never say a person's name
is a reflection of their character...
The chicken curry is this one.
Okay.
But he certainly looks like a prince.
Enjoy your meal.
True. He's definitely more
prince-like than the Prince I know.
Um, excuse me.
We haven't gotten the drinks we ordered.
My apologies.
Here is the cola and
ginger ale you ordered.
Thank you so much!
I'm sorry.
Oh, no worries.
You know, when you stand
next to each other like that,
you look really great.
Like a double prince aura!
Oh, thank you.
I'm serious!
Watching you guys makes
my heart flutter so much!
That's very kind of you.
People call you "Prince"?
Yeah... Because I look like this.
People often mistake me for a boy.
Me too.
People tease me a lot by calling me
"Prince," so I understand how you feel.
For me, my last name is "Oji,"
so there's no way around it.
Oji
Ouji
(Prince)
Oh... Yeah.
Many perceive me to be competent and
reliable, when in truth, I'm not at all.
It really feels like I
don't live up to my name.
But today, you were helping a girl who
was being harassed by a pervert... right?
What?! You saw that?!
Well, we were on the same train, so...
Oh, man. That's embarrassing.
Even then, I let the
culprit get away, so...
It was pretty lame.
It's all right.
I think you still looked very cool.
You're living up to your name.
I never thought of you as a
Prince or anything like that.
I just thought you're a pretty girl.
You know... You're really beautiful.
Whoa, sorry! I said something
really embarrassing!
Since I attend an all-boys school,
I can easily spot girls...
Oh, but not in a perverted way!
No...
It's all right.
Why am I thinking about him
at a time like this?
Ko-chan!
You should have told me you were home.
I just stopped by to grab some clothes.
Oh, my. You should stay a little longer.
Yeah.
Here you go!
I got lots more again for you.
Thanks.
Hey, won't Uncle's store go bankrupt
from giving me so many clothes?
It's fine. He's pretty much
doing it as a hobby, anyway.
He says he likes dressing you up, Ko-chan.
That so?
Besides, Ryu-kun doesn't
wear these kinds of clothes.
It'd be nice if Ryu-kun came
home once in a while, too.
Your dear mother gets so lonely!
Oh, sorry. I gotta get going.
Say hi to Dad for me.
Aww...
Welcome.
Huh? Isn't that the guy they
call the second-year Prince?!
What? Is it really him?!
He doesn't look like a prince to me.
There's rumors that his
family is super rich, and—
Oh, that's true!
My grandpa's company is based in America.
He had a super-smart ancestor
with a bunch of amazing patents.
Huh? Who was his ancestor?!
There's no way we'd have heard of him!
Well, let's find out.
His name was Thomas Edison.
Hello.
What?
Just kiddin'.
Stop believing ridiculous rumors and
focus on your studies, yeah?
Huh? So, he's Edison's descendant?!
Dummy. He was teasing us!
But... He was kinda cool, don't you think?
It seems Ryu-kun broke up
with them, and...
Huh, Senpai?
Jyunshin Shopping District
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Seriously though, what a coincidence.
Comin' from work?
Oh, yes.
I'm feeling strangely self-conscious from
the incident in the library and earlier...
Come to think of it,
the second time I met you,
wasn't I eating Papico then, too?
Oh yeah...
I'm surprised you remembered.
I can't seem to forget it
for whatever reason.
I clearly remember that day.
I don't know, I just can't fully...
figure you out.
That's something I
should be saying to you.
What? Me?!
I'm super easy to read.
Mr. Obvious right here.
Please. You?
Never thought I'd end up
dating you, though.
You just never know how life will go.
Seriously, that's supposed to be my line.
Oof, that was close.
What... should I...?
Y'know this year's summer festival?
Wanna go together?
Yeah.
Then, could you wear a yukata?
Huh? No way.
Oh, come on. I wanna see it.
I don't even own a yukata.
Then I'll buy one.
Wow, there's so many.
Which color?
Purple? Or maybe white?
Hey!
Hmm... Didn't someone say that
black makes women look more beautiful?
I really don't need anything like that!
Just kiddin'.
Whether it's a school
uniform or work clothes,
You can pull off anything, Yoi-chan.
Womanizer.
Wait, what was that?!
Did I hear you insult me just now?
I know you say that to everyone.
Huh? What did ya say?
Philanderer.
What's that?
Yoi-san?!
I wonder if there'll be a stall
with those roasted corncobs.
It's so good, don'cha think?
Is he talking about grilled corn?
I hope they do.
Seriously, he's so irresponsible and
acts incredibly childish sometimes...
But when we hold hands,
it's surprisingly gentle.
It makes me feel like I should think
hard about what to wear
to the summer festival.
The deadline for our
agreement is drawing near.
I wonder what I'm...
what we're... going to decide.
The Side of Me I Don't Know
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis